_______________________________________________________________________________

          Printer Driver Optimization Module for AutoCAD Version  1.17A
                       *** Copyright CANON INC. 2019 ***
_______________________________________________________________________________

Contents

  1. Introduction
  2. System Requirements
  3. Precautions During Installation
  4. Cautions, Limitations and Restrictions


1. Introduction ---------------------------------------------------------------

The Printer Driver Optimization Module for AutoCAD (hereinafter, Optimization 
Module) is software for optimally controlling printing from CAD-use software 
"AutoCAD" of Autodesk, Inc. with imagePROGRAF.

<Trademarks>
- Canon, the Canon logo, and imagePROGRAF are trademarks or registered 
  trademarks of CANON INC.
- Microsoft is a registered trademark of Microsoft Corporation.
- Windows is a trademark or registered trademark of Microsoft Corporation in the 
  U.S. and/or other countries.
- Autodesk, AutoCAD, AutoCAD LT, and other Autodesk product names are 
  trademarks or registered trademarks of Autodesk, Inc. in the United States 
  and other countries. 
- All other trademarks and registered trademarks are the property of their 
  respective owners.


2. System Requirements --------------------------------------------------------

The following hardware and software are recommended for this software.

AutoCAD Versions:
     AutoCAD 2008 - 2019
     AutoCAD LT 2009 - 2019
     DWG TrueView 2008 - 2019

     AutoCAD Architecture 2009 - 2019
     AutoCAD Civil 3D 2011 - 2019
     AutoCAD Electrical 2008 - 2019
     AutoCAD Map 3D 2010 - 2019
     AutoCAD Mechanical 2008 - 2019
     (The operation of all applications is not confirmed.)

Recommended operating environment:
     Any computer running the software listed above 

  Printers:
     Canon imagePROGRAF series
     (Some printers do not support. Please confirm the imagePROGRAF website 
     for the details.)

Printer Driver:
     Canon imagePROGRAF Printer Driver V4.17
     Canon imagePROGRAF Printer Driver V4.43 or later
     (Not available on 32-bit version of Windows.)


3. Precautions During Installation --------------------------------------------

- You must log into Windows as an Administrator before the installation.

- Before performing the installation, close all the other application software.

- If a new support AutoCAD product is installed after the installation of the 
  Optimization Module, reinstall the Optimization Module.


4. Cautions, Limitations and Restrictions -------------------------------------

Note the following limitations when using this software.

- When printing data that includes an extremely large image from a computer 
  with little available memory, it may take time to print, a portion of the 
  image may be missing, or it may otherwise not print properly. 
  If this occurs, try printing after performing the following. 
     - Increase the amount of memory allotted to your computer. 
     - Increase your OS's virtual memory.

